interactive rebase in progress; onto 14d02a4
Last command done (1 command done):
   pick c74d720 # ≡ƒÜÇ Initial Release: AI Career Intelligence System
No commands remaining.
You are currently editing a commit while rebasing branch 'main' on '14d02a4'.
  (use "git commit --amend" to amend the current commit)
  (use "git rebase --continue" once you are satisfied with your changes)

Untracked files:
  (use "git add <file>..." to include in what will be committed)
	gitlog.txt
	push_final_final_final.txt

nothing added to commit but untracked files present (use "git add" to track)
